# **Aryan Barapatre**

+91 8830318024  $\cdot$  aryan18barapatre@gmail.com  $\cdot$  <u>aryanbarapatre.vercel.app</u> Pune, India, 411061

## WEB DEVLOPER AND DESIGNER

Web developer with 2+ years of experience in designing and developing websites. With nearly one year of experience in running a web development and marketing company, along with some expertise in software development and 2D game development. Seeking to expand my skills, pursue new learning opportunities, and conduct research on topics such as Al manager and HYBRID at the esteemed Radboud University.

## **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

#### AISSCE (CBSE) High School Degree (2021 - 2023)

DAV Public School

Graduated with 84.2%

# **Responsive Web Design**

FreeCodeCamp

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/Aryan18/responsive-web-design

# **JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures**

FreeCodeCamp

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/Aryan18/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures

## **SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- React js, Tailwind CSS, Next js
- Node js, MongoDB, Express js
- Three js, Supabase, MySQL
- C++, Godot Engine

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Communication skills
- · Leadership skills
- · Critical and Analytical Thinking
- · Quick Learning
- Adaptability

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Bettle Media April 2023 - Present

# Co Founder and Developer

Founded Bettle Media, a web development and marketing company. As the founder and developer, I have taken on various client projects, interacted with them, and managed my team.

Freelancing Nov 2022 - Present

## Web Designer and Developer

I have successfully undertaken several web development and design projects, including websites related to fitness, gaming, and construction company.

## **PROJECTS**

#### **Funrobics Fithealth**

Designed and developed a responsive website for Funrobics, a fitness company.

Link - funrobics.in

#### **Bettle-Beats**

Developed Bettle-Beats, a music streaming platform. Includes features such as authentication, music player, ability to like songs, and allowing users to upload their own songs.

**Link -** <u>bettle-beats.vercel.app</u>

**Github** - github.com/aryanbarapatre/bettle-beats

## 3D personal portfolio

Developed a 3D personal portfolio website using technologies such as Vite and Three. js.

**Link -** <u>aryanbarapatre.github.io/aryan2portfolio/</u> **Github -** <u>github.com/aryanbarapatre/aryan2portfolio</u>

#### Obstacle avoiding robot

Created an obstacle-avoiding robot using Arduino. Which runs autonomously and changes its direction whenever it encounters an obstacle.

Link - obstacle-avoiding-robot